foreign
[Music]
tips in this video I'll show you how you
can integrate the Facebook lead forms
into the go high level CRM so whenever
someone fills up the Facebook lead form
it is going to send the data to the go
high level CRM and in the go high level
CRM you are going to create a workflow
and using this workflow we are going to
send the SMS or the email to the contact
lead so in this video I am going to show
you how you can create the Facebook lead
ad from the scratch so we are going to
create a sample lead ad into the
Facebook ads manager I will show you how
you can integrate the Facebook ads
account as well as the Facebook page
into the go high level CRM after that we
are going to map the Facebook lead forms
with the go high level fields in many
cases you may need to create custom
fields in the go high level CRM so that
you can map the Facebook lead forms into
the go high level CRM after that we are
going to create a workflow for the
Facebook lead forms so whenever someone
fills up the Facebook lead form it is
going to trigger the workflow and in
this this workflow we are going to
perform different types of actions such
as send SMS send email this automation
is going to help you create a faster
communication with the lead that is
generated from the Facebook ads so let's
see how we can integrate the Facebook
lead ads into the go high level CRM so
we will start with the creation of the
Facebook lead ads so here I am logged
into the dashboard of the ads manager in
Facebook if you do not have ads manager
account you need to create an ads
manager account in Facebook so let's
start with creating a new campaign so
here on the dashboard of the ads manager
you will see the campaigns so I'm going
to create a new campaign click on create
campaign
and this will be a leads campaign so we
are going to collect leads from this
campaign click continue
now here you can add the name of the
campaign so I'm going to
name it as website design this is just a
sample Facebook ads that I am trying to
create to show you how the lead forms
work if you want to add special ad
categories you can select that one
otherwise you can leave it as it is
campaign details it will be option and
we are going to create leads
so we are not going to work on a B test
or Advantage campaign widget so leave it
as it is Click next
the next option will be new leads ad set
so we are going to change the name of
the ad set
so this is the name
and we are going to select instant forms
so we need forms which will collect the
information from the visitor maximize
the number of leads or maximize number
of conversion leads leave it as it is if
you are creating the ads for the first
time it will ask you to agree the terms
and condition that you will see here so
you just need to click on accept the
terms and condition now this is cost per
result goal this is optional so I'm not
going to make any changes here
I'm going to set the daily budget for
this ad campaign
here it shows Indian rupees it will show
your currency there so according to your
currency you can set your daily budget
I'm going to set the start date that
will be 18th
and I'm also going to set the end date
for this campaign
so this will be let's say four days
campaign now here you can set your
audience here I have selected location
India this is the age gender Advantage
Detail targeting you can customize the
targeted audience you can show these ads
to the targeted audience only so here it
shows the estimated daily results
right now let's click on next
the next will be the lead form so I'm
going to change the name here
this is the name of the ad this is the
page on which you want to show this ad
add setup create add now what type of AD
you want single image or video or you
can select Carousel so I'm going to
select single image or video then add
creative from here you can select the
media it will show the media from your
Facebook page if you want to edit you
can simply click on edit
and you will see all the images that you
can select
if you want to change it you can go to
add media
and these are the pages these are the
images from your Facebook page so I'm
going to add new image here so I'm going
to upload it
so this is the image that I want so I'm
going to select this one and click next
click original so this image will be
shown click next
now it is optimizing the image so this
is how it will look so I'm going to
click on done
doubt the next option will be primary
text headline and description so
I'm going to set up some primary text
and the headline
so that I'm just using some Demi content
here
and this is called to action I'm going
to the setup get offer
this is how it will look you will see
the button here
destination
that we are going to create a form here
so let's click on create form
you will see the form type will be more
volume or higher intent or reach
creative so I'm going to set it as more
volume
the intro will be the image I'm going to
upload the image again
and here you will see the headline text
alright so this is the greeting message
after that we are going to ask some
questions these are the basic contact
information such as email address and
the full name so if you want to add you
can simply click on ADD category and you
can add phone number
if you want to add their address you can
also ask for their address State country
postcode user information
per date work information national ID
number so these are the fields that you
can add in the contact information now
before that I want to add one more
question so you can see the option here
add question
and I'm going to add some short answer
so say I want to know the business type
so they can enter their answer here
let's add one more question that will be
multiple choice
do you want
e-commerce website so this is the
question that I'm going to ask them and
the answer will be let's say yes or no
so we have got two different options
here and the next will be contact
information just like this
after that you have privacy policy here
you can add the privacy policy link of
your website so I'll go to the website
here
and let's copy the privacy policy link
and let's put it here
text will be privacy
policy
if you want to add any disclaimer you
can add the disclaimer and after that
message for leads this is a message
after filling up the form and if you
want them to go to your website you can
add the link of your website here so
let's say I want them to go to this
page then I can add the link of this
page here and this will be the text view
website so when they click on it it will
go to that particular website so the
lead ad is created we need to publish it
and after publishing it
all right so here we need to add a
message
all right now click publish
and after publishing it will go to the
review and once the ad is reviewed it
will go live all right now we need to
integrate the Facebook into the go high
level
now I'm logged into the dashboard or the
go high level and I'm using one dummy
sub account to show you how to integrate
the Facebook into the go high level go
to settings
and go to Integrations
now you will see an option here Facebook
and Instagram click on connect
and it will ask you to log into your
Facebook account so I am already logged
in so it is showing me continue as your
name
click continue
now it is asking me to select the
Facebook page so I'm going to select the
Facebook page
and click on connect page
and you can see that the ad account is
connected as well as the page is also
connected all right now let's go to
Facebook form Fields mapping
and you will see an Untitled form here
so I'm going to click on map field now
here you will see the fields that we
created on the Facebook leads form we
created a form field such as do you want
e-commerce website and we added the
options yes and no we ask the question
type of business that was the single
text line then we have these in general
email full name and phone number so we
need to map these fields with the go
high level CRM now for this question I
do not see any field in this list so I
need to create a new field so I'm going
to close this one here
and let's go to custom Fields you will
see the option here custom Fields just
open it
and I'm going to create a custom field
for this question
so here you will see all the standard
fields
let's add a new custom field click on
ADD field now if I'm going to select
this field as a radio select and click
next
and the name will be
do you want e-commerce website
under group I'm going to select general
information
and the answer will be yes
options will be yes and no
click save
let's add one more field that will be
type of business that will be single
line
click next and just name it as business
type
general information
and click save
so we have added two custom Fields here
now let's go back to the integration
Facebook form Fields mapping Let me
refresh it
[Music]
click on map Fields again
and for this particular question I am
going to select
the newly created custom field
for the type of business I'm going to
select the newly created
custom field for the email I can set the
email you can see the those options are
already mapped automatically so I'm
going to save
and you will see a check mark here so
this form is mapped properly now we can
use the Facebook lead forms in the
automation
all right now let's go back
and let's go to automation now we are
going to create a workflow for the
Facebook lead forms so as soon as
someone fills up this form it is going
to send the data into the go high level
and we are going to use that data for
the workflow so let's click on create a
workflow
start from scratch
just name it as Facebook
lead form
and click on trigger
for the trigger we are going to select
Facebook lead form submitted whenever
someone fills up the form on the
Facebook it is going to trigger this
workflow click on ADD filter
for select inform
and this is the Untitled form we forgot
to assign a name for this form so that's
why it is showing Untitled form all
right so this is the form click save
trigger and after that you can create
any kind of workflow let's say wait for
one minute
then send email
so that means after a minute it is going
to send an email
to the contact lead
so here you can add your business name
business email
subject will be
whatever subject line you want to add
you can add your subject line now this
will be a Content hi custom value will
be contact full name so it is going to
show the contact full name
and you can add
the content in the email
so you can add your offers in the email
you can add your packages in the email
and you can also send SMS the same SMS
so it is going to send an SMS there
so this is the SMS that it is going to
send
after that you can wait for the reply
to say
contact reply
SMS or email
so as soon as they send a reply to your
SMS or email you can create a new
workflow here
you can use if else
if the contact reply intent type is
positive you can add another Branch if
the contact reply
content type is
negative
save action so it is going to create two
branches so in case of positive reply
you can add different actions in this
branch in case of negative reply you can
add different actions in this Branch so
you can create a workflow for this
particular Facebook lead forms so that
is going to automate the communication
with the contact leaders as soon as they
fill up the form on the Facebook lead
ads it is going to send the data to the
go high level CRM and the go high level
is going to trigger the workflow that we
created for this Facebook lead ads so
this is how you can create the Facebook
lead ads and you can integrate the
Facebook lead ads into the go high level
CRM for the automation so that's it for
now see you in the next video do not
forget to subscribe to my channel to get
more quick tips about online softwares
and tools if you have any questions
please leave us message in comments
section and press the like button if you
like the video thanks for watching quick
tips
thank you
[Music]